<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Daily Devotional</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard">DashboardActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <string name="menu_home"></string>
    <string name="menu_gallery"></string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow"></string>
    <string name="menu_tools"></string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>

    <string name="text">
    \"And as ye go, preach, saying, The kingdom of heaven is at hand\"
Jesus told his disciples(we) to go and preach the gospel saying THE KINGDOM OF HEAVEN IS AT HAND. We are sent as ambassadors of the kingdom to reveal the kingdom of God to men. Preaching the kingdom is not preaching or talking CONDEMNATION, it is revealing Christ to men. Revealing the nature/ lifestyle of Christ to men, demonstrating the power of Christ to men, Revealing the will and promises of Christ to men and opposing every counsel of Satan on earth.
This is what we are asked to do. God sent Jesus Christ to come and reveal his kingdom to us because Satan has already taken hold of the world and revealing his wrong way of life which opposes the kingdom lifestyle.
That is why you are here. It is time to preach the kingdom of God.
FOR MORE STUDIES: Mark 12 vs. 28, Romans 14 vs. 17, 1Corinthians 4 vs. 20, Luke 8 VS. 1.
MEMORY VERSE: Luke 8 vs. 1 "And it came to pass afterward, that he went throughout every city and village, preaching and shewing the glad tidings of the kingdom of God: and the twelve were with him.
PRAYER: Father, thank you for the salvation of my soul, I receive the boldness, grace and wisdom to preach the kingdom of God in Jesus name, Amen.
    </string>
</resources>
